<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on i ❤️ logic — hrmn.dev</title><link>https://www.hrmn.dev/page/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on i ❤️ logic — hrmn.dev</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><managingEditor>marc@hrmn.dev (Marc Hermann)</managingEditor><webMaster>marc@hrmn.dev (Marc Hermann)</webMaster><atom:link href="https://www.hrmn.dev/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Marc Hermann</title><link>https://www.hrmn.dev/page/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>marc@hrmn.dev (Marc Hermann)</author><guid>https://www.hrmn.dev/page/resume/</guid><description>Summary Software developer with a physics degree (German Diplom, equivalent to MSc) who loves solving problems and making things other people like to use. 4 + 2 years of experience in software development 15 years of experience in creative direction and animation. Based in Berlin, and happy to work remotely as well. Experience Software Development Independent software developer (2020 - now) Award-winning VR experience Mind the Brain!</description></item><item><title>Other things I made</title><link>https://www.hrmn.dev/page/other-things-i-made/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>marc@hrmn.dev (Marc Hermann)</author><guid>https://www.hrmn.dev/page/other-things-i-made/</guid><description>Kicker &amp;amp; Let&amp;rsquo;s Get Married The two that (re)started my journey into animation.
When I wanted to get back into 3D I decided the best way to learn was to make a short film, and so I made Kicker. After the initial idea I read up on film theory, cinematography, editing before actually learning a 3D software, and then started to build the models and animate them. The whole process from idea to finish (ie.</description></item><item><title>Unimportant facts</title><link>https://www.hrmn.dev/page/unimportant-facts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>marc@hrmn.dev (Marc Hermann)</author><guid>https://www.hrmn.dev/page/unimportant-facts/</guid><description>Computers I developed a fascination with computers when I saw the games Zaxxon and Ghostbusters on a Commodore C64 at an older friend&amp;rsquo;s house. A year later my dad brought home my first own computer, bought on a whim at German supermarket chain Aldi: a Commodore C16. I used it to teach myself basic BASIC, to play games, of course, and — would you believe it? — to draw on it with a joystick.</description></item></channel></rss>